We've been given some code
and this exercise asks us
what the each method in this code will return
after it's finished executing
So we call the each method on the variable x
which references an array
We can determine the return value of a method by looking a the ruby documentation
In this case, we will look at the documentation for the Array#each method
We can also copy this code and paste it into IRB to see the return value
So I'll open up IRB
Paste in the code
And when I hit Enter, we can see that the original collection
the array on which we invoked each, is returned
Each will always return the original array, the array that it was called on